worldwebdirectoryindex.com 2019-05-25

# Privacy Policy | Link Building Services | Backlinks Directory

### WorldWebDirectoryIndex.com Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy covers how WorldWebDirectoryIndex.com treats personal information WorldWebDirectoryIndex.com collects and records when you submit your website for inclusion in our web directory.

This policy does not apply to the practices of companies or individuals that WorldWebDirectoryIndex.com campaigns for. This policy also does not apply to people WorldWebDirectoryIndex.com does not employ or manage.

**Information Collection, Sharing and Disclosure** To submit a web site or an article for inclusion, visitor has to open an account at WorldWebDirectoryIndex.com. We ask for website details, article and some personal information. Every information is saved for future reference. Email address is only used for sending email when their website or article is either approved, disapproved or when there is a need to contact you. WorldWebDirectoryIndex.com does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people, affiliated and non affiliated companies. WorldWebDirectoryIndex.com stores your personal information inside our premises under safe custody. Access is limited to those employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information.

**Use of Cookies** **Cookies are used on WorldWebDirectoryIndex.com for the purpose of logging into your account.** The DoubleClick DART cookie is used by Google in the ads served on worldwebdirectoryindex.com websites displaying AdSense for ads. Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy** WorldWebDirectoryIndex.com may amend or update this policy from time to time. Please visit this page to view changes if any.  
  
---  
  
### Sign up for Newsletter

Sign up to get our latest exclusive updates, deals, offers and promotions.
